TAHUANA CIRATI

JR WEB DEVELOPER

- tahuana@gmail.com
- tahuana.com
- **** +1 (416) 428-0567
- **9** Toronto ON Canada
- in tahuana-cirati
- n tahuana

Profile

I am a junior web developer excited to hone my knowledge in JavaScript, Node.js, React, Express, Ruby on Rails and much more!

I have 15 years of experience working on projects within IT and Oil & Gas industries, including 3 years as project analyst, and 6 years in software testing. Result-driven, attention to detail, and strong analytical skills.

When not coding, I can be found reading or testing new delicious recipes.

Skills

LANGUAGES & FRAMEWORKS

JavaScript & Node.js

HTML

CSS

SQL

Ruby on Rails

Express

Bootstrap

DATABASES

MongoDB

PostgreSQL

LIBRARIES

jQuery

React Knex

OTHERS

Project Management Software Testing

Languages

English

Portuguese

Education

Lighthouse Labs

Immersive Full-Stack Web Development Bootcamp 2017

IBMEC Business School

Postgraduate Project Management 2013

UFRJ - **Federal University of Rio de Janeiro**Bachelor's Degree Computer Science 2001

Projects

tahuana.com

Aug 2017 to Aug 2017

- My personal website.
- Developed using HTML, CSS and Bootstrap.

Pairwise Jul 2017 to Jul 2017

- A project-driven mentoring platform built for experienced devs and learners to collaborate and grow.
- Developed using Ruby on Rails and PostgreSQL.

Resource Wall

Jun 2017 to Jun 2017

- Allow learners to save learning resources like tutorials, blogs and videos in a central place that is publicly available to any user.
- Developed using HTML, EJS, jQuery, AJAX, JavaScript and Sass in front-end, and Node, Express, PostgreSQL and Knex in back-end.

Tweeter Jun 2017 to Jun 2017

- Tweeter is a simple, single-page Twitter clone.
- Developed using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery and AJAX in front-end, and Node, Express and MongoDB in back-end.

SGI Oct 2015 to Jun 2016

- Project to restructure the individual metering segment for Supergasbras, including: system improvements and process revision (metering, billing, delivery, collection, customer records).
- Worked as PMO supporting Project Manager on methodology, documentation, project schedule, and weekly status report.

Employment

Supergasbras Project Analyst Rio de Janeiro, Brazil Feb 2014 to Jun 2016

- Participated in the corporate PMO launching.
- Worked as team member of PMO group, supporting 7 projects simultaneously, within a program to ERP system implementation, to successful completion within the allocated time.
- Supported 10+ Project Managers in all aspects of the project lifecycle.

Supergasbras

Business Technology Analyst

Rio de Janeiro, Brazil Jun 2011 to Feb 2014

Rio de Ianeiro. Brazil

- Defined methodology and templates for software testing in Corporate IT.
- Led quality assurance of 5 softwares systems delivered by Corporate IT.
- Managed outsourced test team, including 4 professionals assigned in different projects.

Avanti Prima System Analyst

Sep 2006 to Jun 2011

Participated as tester analyst in 5 software development projects in Petrobras' IT.

- Led software quality assurance with one report, focusing on small projects.
- Trained new members on test team.

Certifications

PMI/PMP - Project Management Professional - 2013-2019

BSTQB/CTFL - Certified Tester, Foundation Level – From 2008